<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Blood Brothers Database</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fam_detail">Familiar detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fam_compare">Familiar comparison</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer close</string>
    <string name="help_text">
<![CDATA[
        <b>Q: What are the different stats type (Base, Max, PE, POPE)?</b> <br/>
        A: <br/> 
        Base is the stats of a familiar at capture or from a pact (at LV1). 
            It is the lowest stats that you can see of a familiar  <br/><br/>
        Max is the stats of a familiar fully leveled up (i.e. LV 70 for a Rare, 
            or LV 99 for an Epic), without evolution or adding crystals. <br/><br/>
        PE (Perfect Evolution) is the highest stats of a familiar that can be achieved by 
            leveling up and evolving, AND without adding crystals. For example, to make a 
            PE Epic 4 familiar you need 8 Rare 1 familiars<br/><br/>
        POPE (Perfect Over Perfect Evolution) is similar to PE, but with the maximum number of crystals added. 
            This is generally 400 crystals for 8-card evolutions and 100 for 2-card evolutions. <br/><br/>
        
        The POPE stats are obtained by adding 665.5 to the corresponding PE stats. In the game, most of the time this is rounded up to 666, 
            but sometimes it is rounded down to 665. This app use 666 to calculate POPE, so some familiars\' POPE stats maybe off by 1
            (i.e. All-Seeing Keeper II\'s POPE AGI should be 17133, not 17134)<br/><br/>
            
        <b>Q: How often is this app\'s data updated?</b> <br/>
        A: This app pulls all data from the Blood Brothers Wikia in real time, so the data is always up-to-date. <br/><br/>
        
        <b>Q: I like this app!</b> <br/>
        A: I\'m glad to hear it. Please rate it on the Play Store :)<br/><br/>
        
        <b>Q: This app sucks!/I found a bug/This is not useful/I have a suggestion...</b> <br/>
        A: Please drop me a line at chinho.dev@gmail.com and let me know how I can improve it. Thank you :)<br/><br/>
      ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_tier_table">TierTableActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>
